<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on BwdFwd</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on BwdFwd</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OF LOVE AND FEAR AND COURAGE AND HUMANS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/kaleidoscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/kaleidoscope/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of days ago, I was sitting in a cafe, talking to a friend about affection, courage, and fear of the future. As we were talking, we started to discuss emotions and their relationship to Zukunftsangst. One particular question we tried to answer got stuck in my head: ‘How can we be certain that feelings and love will remain for years?’ Within that question sits in my opinion Zukunftsangst. We talked about this for a while, but it continued to work in me over the past days. I don&amp;rsquo;t think there is a right or a wrong answer, but here is my view on this question.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design Elements Demo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/design_demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/design_demo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a demo page showcasing all the different text elements and styles used on this site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This page demonstrates various markdown elements to help visualize the design. It includes headings, text formatting, blockquotes, code blocks, lists, tables, and mathematical equations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;subsection-example&#34;&gt;Subsection Example&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a third-level heading with some regular paragraph text. The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog. This sentence contains all letters of the alphabet and helps demonstrate font rendering.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graffiti</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/graffiti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/graffiti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;height: 2em;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;except from a book, that may or may not be written&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height: 3em;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Writing something, somewhere in a public place has always been a go-to tool for those without any other means of resistance to stick it to the current regime. But since the advent of nano-tech coatings and fast clean-up drones, spray and paint have lost their “fuck-the-system” value. But the world keeps spinning and scientific knowledge generally doesn’t want to be tied up like a hooker too careless to agree to some mild bondage play up in the back alley brothels on the soft underbelly of Tokyos shadow world. Now the tool of choice is microbial bio-paint. A mixture of a calcium-rich deployment substrate and lab engineered bacteria that have all but two functions spliced from their genetic composition.&#xA;The first converts the deployment fuel into highly corrosive fluorinated acid that decomposes anything including hardened glass into a workable canvas to spread “the message”. The second, is a highly optimised gene expression protocol that recombines the available molecules from the canvas and the deployment substrate into a almost indestructible calcium-silicate crust, that remains of a surface longer than the time humans have populated rock-3.&#xA;Put the fully enriched mixture anywhere and within seconds the gene edited cells will engrave themselves into the surface. Used carefully, you can write anything anywhere and make sure it remains there to be seen until the surface gets demolished. More expensive versions also embed any combination of fluorescence particles into the mix to make artists mental arithmetics against the system pop even more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared and sharded time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shared_sharded_time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shared_sharded_time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;height: 3em;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height: 3em;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;The good things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;England.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;height: 3em;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height: 3em;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weights</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/weights/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/weights/</guid>
      <description>&lt;video &#xA;    width=&#34;80%&#34; &#xA;    &#xA;    autoplay&#xA;    loop&#xA;    muted&#xA;    style=&#34;display: block; margin: var(--spacing-base) auto; border-radius: var(--border-radius);&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;source src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/videos/weights.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;&#xA;    Your browser does not support the video tag.&#xA;&lt;/video&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
